{	"div":
	[	
		{
			"Problem":"6276/47",
			"answer":"6276/47",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"7171/84",
			"answer":"7171/84",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5849/31",
			"answer":"5849/31",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"3326/97",
			"answer":"3326/97",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"5930/73",
			"answer":"5930/73",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"34.63/0.96",
			"answer":"34.63/0.96",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"98.98/98",
			"answer":"98.98/98",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"406.4/0.58",
			"answer":"406.4/0.58",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"4.985/11",
			"answer":"4.985/11",
			"status":"unsolved"
		},

		{
			"Problem":"40.23/1.4",
			"answer":"40.23/1.4",
			"status":"unsolved"
		}
	]
}